question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "&quot;Resident Evil 7&quot; is the first first-person Resident Evil game.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The game &quot;Pocket Morty&quot; has a Morty called &quot;Pocket Mortys Morty&quot;?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
